Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Once upon a time, in a certain place...
Prehistoric creatures full of personality!
Tirano, Stego, Ammonite,Trilobite.
They've been saying "hi" for 500 million years.
Prehistory! Everybody Say (Roar!)
Ancient, Alright! Future, FLY High!
A herd of mammoths! Run!
Thud thud thud thud! On your marks, get set, go!
Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Dive deep into serious learning,
Playing for real.
The universe begins with passion.
Super happy!
Serious Mosasaurus Picture-Story Show
Huh, is this...
Yes, that's what it is.
Wait, what do you mean?
WELCOME TO THE WORLD OF SERIOUS PALEOTOLOGY!
Hey, wait a second!
Huh? What is this place?
A picture-story show in this day and age?
Ah,
Dino!
''And so, as Hebitaro became friends with everyone,what fell from his eyes
wasn't tears,
but scales''.
''Snakes don't have eyelids;
their eyes are covered with transparent scales''.
''And that's where the saying
'scales falling from one's eyes' comes from''.
Okay, here's some chocolate!
Yay! Give me some!
Me too!
Looks delicious!
Thank you, Dino-kun!
Thanks!
What is that guy doing?
He's trying his best in his own way as an extracurricular activity for the Paleontology Club.
Wait, aren't snakes modern creatures?
You can't entirely say that.
What do you mean?
Step right up, everyone!
Next up is this picture-story show!
The Story of Mosasaurus
"The Story of Mosasaurus"
P-President Tetori!
A dinosaur!
Awesome!
Mosasaurus is not a dinosaur!
It's a reptile that lived in the water!
Why are you getting so frustrated?!
Covered in fine,
snake-like scale skin, it was indeed a reptile.
And Mosasaurus,
even ate sharks!
Why are you scared too?!
Its ability to eat sharks was thanks to the secret in its teeth and jaws!
Mosasaurus had sharp teeth, up to 100 of them!
And on its upper jaw...
there were actually two rows of teeth lined up!
Whoa...
Wait, you're actually getting into it?!
Mosasaurus used its double-jointed jaws
that opened wide to bite
and swallow prey whole!
So cool!
He is totally drawn in!
Relatives of Mosasaurus were also abundant in Cretaceous Japan!
Perhaps a Mosasaurus is...
sleeping right near us,
beneath our feet!
Mosasaurus are the best!
He is completely captivated now...
In fact Mosasaurus is
actually a relative of snakes!
Features like these jaws and teeth
are the biggest proof that Mosasaurus evolved from the same ancestor as snakes!
Dino, come over here!
P-President?
How about it?
Isn't it wonderful that relatives of Mosasaurus are still around us today?
Oh! It's Dino-kun's picture-story show!
Snakes are amazing!
Dino-kun is amazing too!
Amazing!
Goodness...
I really can't compete with President Tetori.
Dino, are you crying?
Scales fell from my eyes!